I think I have a big deal.
Uh...
Meow.
Hi. There, there.
All right.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Show it to baby. We've got snacks.
No, thanks. I don't need any...
Chota Baby, what's the matter?
Just trying to think of a good present to make for Dad's Day.
Dad's Day?
A talisman?
It might be a little difficult, but I can do it.
How cool. Allow me to help you out, then.
No, thanks.
This is something I have to do on my own.
Anyway, that's what happened.
Wow, a Father's Day present, huh?
What a thoughtful little guy.
I'm looking forward to seeing what he finally comes up with for me.
Aren't talismans those protective charm-like things I see humans carry around a lot?
You do?
Can you tell if they work or not and to what extent?
They don't work at all.
They all go up in flames along with the humans gripping them.
Sounds like a first-hand testimony.
You say that as if all talismans are full of crap, but they actually work quite well with proper magic.
They do?
What I don't get is how a talisman is supposed to show someone you appreciate their yavos.
Okay, I'm confused. Which conversation are you in?
Huh? You know, we're talking about Tits Day.
Uh, seriously? I need to go lie down.
Let me see.
Whoa, that's a lot.
Looks like the official ones are sold out.
The ratings are so low, I can't tell if they're good.
That does it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, first I take a unicorn's horn and wyvern's blood,
ground branches from a tree with a human face,
and one dried blue rose.
That's that.
Now I let everything stew for an hour and wait for the smell to fade.
Then I'll cast the boning spell and it should be complete.
Oh! Shanta Baby, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I can help you a tiny bit.
Please don't.
I promise I'm fine.
Okay, try again.
Is everything okay up there?
Nice going, bro.
Man, this new event quest is a beast.
At this rate, I'm gonna get KO'd.
Yeah, you are.
It's not that bad.
Hey, Shanta, what's bugging you?
Hmm?
Um, nothing.
Why do you think I'm bugged?
Just a feeling I get.
To be honest,
I'm trying to make a talisman for a Father's Day present,
but it's not going well.
I see.
I followed the steps written in the grimoire exactly,
so I don't get why it isn't working.
I want to show my Father how good I am at something,
but I keep messing up.
I just need to hurry and become a real-life mage.
Look at it like playing a game.
A game?
When you fight enemies that you know are a higher level,
you don't exactly expect to win, right?
Yeah, that's true.
So, if you really want to defeat them,
you should try thinking about the developers' feelings at the time.
The developers?
Yeah.
Games don't just appear out of nowhere.
They're programmed worlds,
and they only operate exactly as the developers intended.
So then, try to imagine what they were feeling
when they designed a level.
What did they want their players to do?
If you can get inside that mindset,
then the instructions on how to clear the game
will become blatantly obvious.
That's the part you always have a problem with, too.
When you're on the developer's side,
you find that it's a huge pen in the A
to figure out ways to mislead your players.
Think like a developer.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
I'll go ahead and give it another try.
Hmm? Hmm.
There has to be some kind of condition required
that's not written in the grimoire.
But what could it be?
Hmm.
All right.
It's done!
Look how I look!
I finished the talisman!
Oh.
Great, Shota Baby.
How'd you do it?
I thought about the person who wrote the grimoire,
and when I looked up where it was written,
I found out it was written in what we call the Dead Sea,
which is below sea level.
So I decided to recreate the very same environment
by increasing the air pressure in my room,
and that's when I discovered the secret.
Hmm.
Never mind, forget it!
Why am I slowly my guns to a demon?
Huh?
Ah!
Did he like the present?
Yeah, sure, but...
he said I need to work harder.
No, Shota, you've worked very hard.
Happy Breast Friends Day!
Hey, you still haven't let me out!
Shoulder massage tickets? What for?
It's a present.
For what? It's not my birthday or anything.
Because it's Father's Day.
Oh, you think I'm a father now?
Mm-hmm.
Like, instead of a mother?
Oh, no, what's the matter, Miss Kobayashi?
Toru, I do believe I've caught a cold.
A cold?
I've heard that phrase before, but I still don't understand.
You mean dragons don't catch colds?
There's no way a tiny human virus could survive inside the furnace that is my body.
Must be nice.
Well, time for me to go to work.
Are you well enough to go?
That's cute.
Like, they'd ever let me take off work for something as minor as my...
Whoa.
Miss Kobayashi!
What's that mean?
Should I bang on your chest and blow it in your mouth?
I pray that you won't.
But I won't be able to go into work, so I need to call and let them know.
I'll do it for you!
Oh, no.
Well, let her know I have everything under control, and we hope she feels better.
Okay.
Um, Mr. Takuya?
Miss Kobayashi just took some medicine and already fell asleep, but...
Is there anything else I can do for her?
I'm afraid I don't have much experience with sick humans, so I'm not sure what would help her most.
Hmm.
You could always try to shrink the germs so that they're easier to kill.
I could do that, but I'd likely destroy her body in the process.
Then maybe...
Be her nurse?
That's right.
What's important...
I get it now!
What she needs is a healthy dose of multivitamate power!
Miss Kobayashi needs me, and I will do everything I can to help!
I will protect her body and destroy her viral enemy!
So, um, is that right?
What do nurses do?
Shh!
Why don't you just feed her something that can detoxify her insides?
Like charcoal or some yummy limestone?
Miss Kobayashi isn't a fire dragon, or a brick oven for that matter.
I know plenty of ways to bring about human illness, but I know nothing about curing them.
You should learn to fend them off, too!
All you have to do is feed her something that's easily digested, keep her head cool, and then wipe her sweat when it gets gross.
Ow!
Thank you!
The fact that it takes three attempts to get a reasonable answer says a lot about who my friends are.
I wonder what she means by easily digested.
Let's see.
I can digest just about anything, so it's hard to know it's good.
Rice gruel?
That looks like it's easy to make.
We need yogurt.
I think I saw Kana put some in the fridge.
Udon, gelatin, bananas.
Hmm.
That just leaves something sweet.
Bone apple tea!
Yummy rice gruel!
She went out of her way to make it for me, so I guess it would be rude to say it looks too weird to eat.
Now's probably not the best time to teach her the concept of foods that go well together.
I'm so glad you like it!
Next time, all you have to do is follow the recipe.
Promise?
Okay!
It seems like you're sweating an awful lot.
Would you mind if I wiped it off for you?
Huh?
What is happening?
My heart is racing all of a sudden.
Miss Kobayashi always comes off as such a strong, reliable person.
This is my first time seeing her so vulnerable.
She's gonna be okay, isn't she?
I've known whole villages destroyed by epidemics.
I've seen entire nations wiped out by them, too.
You're gonna get better.
I just wish I knew for sure.
I don't want anything that's precious to me destroyed.
I suppose everything breaks eventually.
That's especially true around me, since I can break just about anything.
All right!
I'm home!
Hello, Kana.
Huh?
Please watch over, Miss Kobayashi.
Mm-hmm.
There are medicines that grant immortality, but I know Miss Kobayashi would never go for those.
I have to at least find something that can cure the illness she has.
That might be harder to find out here, but...
Go do it!
I won't let you down, Miss Kobayashi!
Hang in there!
Oh, man.
I feel so much better after some good rest.
Better?
Are you not well?
I'll be okay after I get some medicine and some sleep for a few days.
That's amazing!
Hmm?
Where's Toru?
There you are.
What's the matter?
You look exhausted.
Here you go.
I searched everywhere.
Um, what is that?
It's medicine that's supposed to be very effective for cults.
Okay, but is it safe?
There's nothing weird like chicken breath is...
Hmm.
Thanks.
I'll try them.
Hmm.
They work.
You mean that?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
This is incredible.
Oh, thank goodness!
Honestly?
I'm worried about you.
I don't know if it's working or not.
That would work.
But that look on her face has to be some of the best medicine in the world.
Hey, Toru?
Thank you.
What the heck is out of my head and growing out of my face?
Uh-oh.
Maybe it's a side effect?
The medicine was for beast bulk.
But you look cute.
How am I supposed to go to work like this?
Jin então é um, e eu ?
Ah!
that's a doll
did someone leave it it looks expensive and very good quality i think she's pretty
we should probably return it right i bet they'll be by tomorrow to pick it up
no one showed up for it then i'll have to go look for them i should ask around first
you're coming too right if i don't i'll just worry
hey oh it's the candy shop lady do you know whose doll this might be i don't okay are you and mr
takitzer together because it kind of looks like he's your boyfriend what are you talking about
of course we're not together um yes we are you said you wanted to go together to find the owner
that's not what she meant let's try asking that kid too
she's not listening i guess she's an orphan it's just hard to track down one specific person
maybe they didn't forget it but intentionally left it at the store for someone to find
no i'll find them
we've looked everywhere i think we should turn it over to the police
is there anybody else you know that you think we should ask
i brought us someone to help out this is kobayashi hey there i heard what's going on
but i don't think there's anything i can do alulu
please if anyone can help it's you
so this is the kobayashi that alulu mentioned
she looks normal but what's with that blonde maid behind her
she's totally chill like she's used to all this does she wear that uniform every day
this woman is definitely bad news
let's take a picture of it and post it on the internet
but you know it'd be even more helpful as if you could use your magic powers to sharpen your sense of smell
oh right
why are you suddenly forcing her into puppy play
huh i'm not
have you been training her this whole time
slow down
you're wrong none of that is true
huh
the only one allowed to receive training is me
you're making it worse shut up
okay i think i've got the scent
you what hold on
hmm
elulu
here this is for you
what is it are you sure
i made it just for you elulu
i hope you like it
thank you so much
i'll cherish it always
hey
do you know where we're going
we're heading into the next town over
i'm sorry you followed me this far already
you can go home if you want
are you sure
okay
see ya
yeah
is it still farther
did they really mean to leave it
it was still warm when they picked it up
they must have been holding it until that moment
what do i do
it'll get wet
no
the sun's starting to faint too
i thought you went home
it was getting cloudy
i figured it was going to rain
listen
long ago
i abandoned the doll like this
one that i loved very much
i regret leaving it
i'd go back and get it if i could
and i'm pretty positive
someone feels the same for her
well then
we need to make sure that we find our owner
really
found her
she's over there
ilulu
hello kobayashi
where did she just come from
turns out that doll was a custom order
so i was able to pin down the store that originally made it
when i asked them about the owners
they said they visited the shop often for maintenance
so that means they remembered them fondly
so then
so your doll's no longer homeless
and they said we could bring it by
here i've got their address
just who are you anyway
i'm sorry for causing you so much trouble
you see
i left it there on purpose
i thought maybe when you found it that
you'd put it on display
i'm in high school now
and my friends were teasing me
they told me it was childish
and i had to throw it away or else
but i
i've regretted it ever since i left her
i know it's too late now
that's not true
if you can take her back
then you should
i'm sure she'd love it
if you welcomed her home
i'm sorry
welcome home
come on ilulu
it's time for you to take a bath
okay
well thanks
that was very nice of you
i appreciate you going with her
well uh
i didn't really want
take
don't you need a bath too
take one with me
what are you doing
go put your clothes on
i told you i'm taking a bath
you have to take your clothes off for that
okay but leave me alone
to be young again
miss kubiyoshi
ta-da
it's you
but as a cute doll
you like it
no it's weird
and why is it in your shirt
cause he finds it comforting
comforting how
come here i'll show you
you're out of control
and why is it in your shirt
no it's complete
oh
yeah
man
Ilulu, how's your part-time job?
It's fun. We have a visitor that comes around all the time.
A regular, huh?
Yeah, but sometimes they try to get a free meal and put us in a spot.
Huh. Is that person doing okay?
It's not a person. It's a cat.
First week on Booze Rotten.
Aries.